<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nix Blog - Tutorials, Opinions, Rants</title>
    <link>https://davidnix.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nix Blog - Tutorials, Opinions, Rants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 19:17:24 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidnix.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post Title 1</title>
      <link>https://davidnix.github.io/post/test_post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 19:17:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidnix.github.io/post/test_post1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://davidnix.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 16:18:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidnix.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;No, I’m not the antagonist from Disney&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://disney.wikia.com/wiki/David_Nix&#34;&gt;Tomorrowland&lt;/a&gt;.   Although I would like to rule a futuristic utopia, I’m actually a software engineer.  I live in Denver, CO with my amazing wife and soon-to-be daughter.  I love startups and the craft of software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the day, I code iOS and &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt;.  My latest goal is to convince startups to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/DavidNix/modern-web-apps-in-go&#34;&gt;use Go&lt;/a&gt;.  I’ve fallen out of love with Ruby on Rails for reasons you’ll find littered on the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blog is about code and startups.  And it’s brand new.  So, I’m not sure how it’s going to evolve.  I hope to self-publish a book or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;My philosophy aligns with Bob Martin, Martin Fowler, Rob Pike, and Ken Thompson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I embrace the unix philosophy.  Do one thing well and let me compose using libraries that also embrace the  unix way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a unit test freak.  If I can’t test it, I’ll find another way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a rabid fan of Google’s Go programming language (aka Golang).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;My dying words will be “composition over inheritance”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;consulting:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Consulting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am available for part-time consulting for iOS.  I have experience architecting iOS apps for long-term maintainability and stability.  Please contact me using a method below.  My first born and employment at &lt;a href=&#34;http://cirrusmd.com&#34;&gt;CirrusMD&lt;/a&gt; prevent me from contact work.  And yes, recruiters, that means I’m not available for full-time hire either.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>